AI agents are powerful.
They can trade crypto and manage money.
But what if they make mistakes?
What if a hacker tricks them?
50 million dollars lost to AI exploits in 2024.
We need a safety net.
Human oversight for AI financial actions.
Introducing PolicyGuard Agent.
Human-in-the-loop AI with Hedera integration.
Here's how it works.
AI proposes, PolicyGuard assesses,
Human approves, Hedera executes.
Risk-based approval.
Low amounts auto-approved.
Medium and high require human verification.
Let's see it in action.
First, a small payment.
Alice pays Bob 2 HBAR for coffee.
Low risk, below threshold.
Auto-approved and executed.
Transaction logged to Hedera.
Now a medium amount.
Alice sends 30 HBAR to a contractor.
Challenge created.
Requires human approval.
AI cannot proceed alone.
Alice reviews the transaction.
Verifies recipient and amount.
Approves the challenge.
Only then does it execute.
Safety enforced by code.
Now a high-value payment.
40 HBAR for equipment.
Multi-signature required.
Two of three executives must approve.
CFO approves.
Business purpose verified.
CTO approves.
Technical validation passed.
Threshold reached.
Transaction executes.
No single point of failure.
Every decision is logged.
Immutable audit trail on Hedera.
Regulators can verify compliance.
Insurance can audit policies.
No one can tamper with history.
PolicyGuard Agent.
Safe AI. Human Control. Immutable Proof.
Built for Hedera.
Ready for production.
Thank you.